vyou.com 2013-03-27

# VYou

**Last Updated:** October 2010

Virtual Labs Inc has developed this Privacy Policy to indicate the actions it is willing to take with respect to your privacy. These privacy policies (the "Privacy Policy") are intended to describe for you, as an individual who is a user of [www.vyou.com](http://www.vyou.com/) or our services, the information we collect, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures.

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our website or services or transacting business with us. By using our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us.

**Information We Collect About You**

In General. We may collect personal information that can identify you, such as your name and email address, and other information that does not identify you. When you provide personal information through our website, the information may be sent to servers located in the United States and other countries around the world.

  * **Information you provide.** We may collect and store any personal information you enter on our website or provide to us in some other manner, including personal information that may be contained in any video, message or other submission you upload or post to the website. This includes identifying information, such as your name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number; your likeness; and, if you transact business with us, financial information such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information). We also may request information about your interests and activities, your gender and age, and other demographic information.
  * **Information about others.** We may also collect and store personal information about other people that you provide to us. If you use our website to send others (friends, relatives, colleagues, etc.) a product as a gift, information that may interest them or messages (such as invitations) through our system, we may store your personal information, and the personal information of each such recipient. Similarly, if you use our website to upload, share and/or distribute content (including videos, comments, messages or other submissions), and such content contains personal information about others, such information may be stored in order to allow for such uploading, sharing and/or distribution.
  * **Information from other sources.** We may also periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from other business partners, contractors and other third parties. Examples of information that we may receive include: updated delivery and address information, purchase history, and additional demographic information.

Use of cookies and other technologies to collect information. We use various technologies to collect information from your computer and about your activities on our site.

  * **Information collected automatically.** We automatically collect information from your browser when you visit our website. This information includes your IP address, your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us (see " cookies" below), and the referring website address.
  * **cookies** When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more  cookies, to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site, such as the web pages you visit, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our site. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline  cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on our website.
  * **Other Technologies.** We may use standard Internet technology, such as web  beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of our site. We also may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our website visitors to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities.
  * **Information collected by third-parties.** We may allow third-parties, including our authorized service providers, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as  cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Unless expressly stated otherwise, our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies ([www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)).

**How We Use The Information We Collect**

In General. We may use information that we collect about you to:

  * enforce our conditions and terms
  * display and develop advertising and other content designed to match your interests and preferences on our site and other sites;
  * deliver the products and services that you have requested;
  * manage your account and provide you with customer support;
  * communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or other third parties;
  * perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others;
  * verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes;
  * manage our business and
  * perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

Financial information. We may use financial information or payment method to process payment for any purchases, subscriptions or sales made on our website, to protect against or identify possible fraudulent transactions, and otherwise as needed to manage our business.

Please review "Your Choices About Collection and Use of Your Information" below.

**With Whom We Share Your Information**

We want you to understand when and with whom we may share personal or other information we have collected about you or your activities on our website or while using our services.

Personal information. We do not share your personal information with others except as indicated below or when we inform you and give you an opportunity to [opt out](http://vyou.com/user/mysettings?t=tab3) of having your personal information shared. We may share personal information with:

  * **Authorized service providers:** We may share your personal information with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include fulfilling orders, processing credit card payments, delivering packages, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, supporting our website functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through our website. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.
  * **Business partners:** To the extent any personal information is contained in any video, message or other user submission, such information. When you make purchases, reservations or engage in promotions offered through our website or our services, we may share personal information with the businesses with which we partner to offer you those products, services, promotions, contests and/or sweepstakes. When you elect to engage in a particular merchant’s offer or program, you authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that merchant.
  * **Direct mail partners.** From time to time we may share our postal mailing list with selected providers of goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive mailings from these providers, you can notify us at any time by [clicking here](http://vyou.com/user/mysettings?t=tab3).
  * **Other Situations.** We also may disclose your information:

    * In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us, in our sole discretion.
    * When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce our website terms and conditions or other agreements or policies.
    * In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

Any third parties to whom we may disclose personal information may have their own privacy policies which describe how they use and disclose personal information. Those policies will govern use, handling and disclosure of your personal information once we have shared it with those third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. If you want to learn more about their privacy practices, we encourage you to visit the websites of those third parties. These entities or their servers may be located either inside or outside the United States.

**Aggregated and non-personal information.** We may share aggregated and non-personal information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We may also share it with third parties to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our websites and on websites of third parties. We may combine non-personal information we collect with additional non-personal information collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors to our website and the most popular features or services accessed. This information does not contain any personal information and may be used to develop website content and services that we hope you and other users will find of interest and to target content and advertising.

**Notice Regarding User-Generated-Content**

**We do not monitor, screen, or otherwise filter user submissions to the website, nor do we glean or otherwise scrape personal information from any such submissions; however, to the extent that any video, message or other user submission contains personal information (whether name, likeness, address, telephone number or otherwise, and whether such information pertains to the submitter or someone else), such personal information may be viewed by other users of the website.** See "User Submissions", below.

**Third-Party Websites**

There are a number of places on our website or through our services where you may click on a link to access other websites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. For example, if you click on an advertisement or a search result on our website, you may be taken to a website that we do not control. These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those websites. We recommend that you consult the privacy statements of all third-party websites you visit by clicking on the "privacy" link typically located at the bottom of the webpage you are visiting.

**How You Can Access Your Information**

If you have an online account with us, then by logging into your account you have the ability to review and update your personal information online. You can also review and update your personal information by contacting us. More information about how to contact us is provided below.

If you have an online account with us, you also may elect to close your account at any time by contacting customer support at: [support@vyou.com](mailto:support@vyou.com). You will not be able to sign in to our website or access any of your personal information after you close your account. However, you can open a new account at any time. If you close your account, we may still retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to enforce our terms and condition, collection of fees due, , take actions we deem necessary to protect the integrity of our website or our users, including the prevention of fraud, or take other actions otherwise permitted by law. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties’ policies.

**Your Choices About Collection And Use Of Your Information**

  * You can choose not to provide us with certain information. To the extent you make such election, your choice may result in you being unable to use certain features of our website because such information may be required in order for you to register as a member; purchase services or products;, participate in a sweepstakes, survey, contest or promotion; ; ask a question; or initiate other transactions on our website.
  * You may be given a choice when you register on our website as to whether you want to receive newsletters about updates to products, special offers, email messages and/or or types of communications containing special distributions of content by us. At any time you can choose to no longer receive commercial or promotional emails or newsletters from us by clicking on the following link and entering the email address associated with your account: [click here](http://vyou.com/user/mysettings?t=tab3). You also will be given the opportunity, in any commercial e-mail that we send to you, to [opt out](http://vyou.com/user/mysettings?t=tab3) of receiving such messages in the future. It may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out request. We may send you other types of transactional and relationship e-mail communications, such as service announcements, administrative notices, and surveys, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. Please note that, changing information in your account, or otherwise opting out of receipt of promotional email communications will only affect future activities or communications from us. If we have already provided your information to a third party (such as a credit card processing partner or an event provider) before you have changed your preferences or updated your information, you may have to change you preferences directly with that third party.

**Protective Measures We Take With Respect to Your Personal Information**

We take certain security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. In addition, we use encryption in the transmission of your sensitive personal information between your system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal information.

No system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or other communications will always remain secure. Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their personal information and should avoid sending personal information through insecure email. Please refer to the Federal Trade Commission’s website at <http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data.shtm> for information about how to protect yourself against identity theft.

**User Submissions**

We may provide areas on our websites where you can post information about yourself and others and communicate with others; upload content (e.g. audio files, videos, pictures, blogs etc.); and post comments or reviews of content found on the Website. Such postings are governed by our [Terms and Conditions of Use](http://vyou.com/index/tos). In addition, such postings may appear when searches are executed on the subject matter of your posting or on other websites. Also, any voluntary disclosure by you of personal information on publicly-viewable web pageswill be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post. We strongly urge you to use a high degree of discretion and caution with respect to your personal information. Once you have posted information, you may not be able to edit or delete such information.

**Children’s Privacy**

Our website is a general audience site, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

**Visiting Our Websites From Outside The United States**

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on or via our website from residents of the United States. If you are visiting our website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this privacy policy.

**No Rights Of Third Parties**

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the website.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices, policies, procedures, protective measures and services. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "Last Updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. To the extent that we determine such changes are reasonably likely to result in material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will notify you by sending an email to the email address you most recently provided us in your account, profile or registration (unless we do not have such an email address), and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our website. We recommend that you check our website from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies.

**How To Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information-handling practices, or if you would like to request information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, please contact us by email or postal mail as follows:

**Virtual Labs Inc** 560 Broadway, Suite 402

New York, NY 10012 [privacy@vyou.com](mailto:privacy@vyou.com)

©2010 Virtual Labs Inc. All rights reserved.

**Linked information:**

**Cookies:**

A cookie is a record keeping mechanism in the form of a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer. Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie will expires if you close your browser. Session cookies are utilized to make navigation on our website easier. A persistent cookie will remain on your hard drive for an extensive period of time.

As an example, when you sign in to our website, your user or member ID will be recorded, as well as the name on your user or member account in the cookie file on your computer. We also may record your password in this cookie file, if you indicated that you would like your password saved for automatic sign-in. For security purposes, any usernames, passwords, and other user or member account-related data that we store in such cookies will be encrypted. In the case of sites and services that do not use a user or member ID, the cookie will contain a unique identifier. We may allow our authorized service providers to serve cookies from our website so that they mayassist us in various activities, such as doing analysis and research on the effectiveness of our site, content and advertising.

You may delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings. (Click "Help" in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions.) If you do so, some of the features and services of our website may not function properly.

There are third party companies that may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with advertisements we allow to be displayed on our website.

Such third parties may include advertising companies, ad networks and other third parties. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties, but they may collect information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they deliver, and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to the advertised websites. They also may combine this information with personal information they collect from you. The collection and use of that information is subject to the third-party’s privacy policy. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies (www.networkadvertising.org).

**Web Beacons:**

Web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages (or in email) and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access cookies. They are graphics about the size of the period at end of this sentence with a unique identifier. They are also known as as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs.

Web beacons may be used to count users who have visited certain pages of a website, to communicate with or delivercookies, and to understand usage patterns. We also may receive an anonymous identification number if you come to our site from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website.
